<help>
		<!-- Timeout message -->
		<message id="timeout"><![CDATA[Your request has timed out. Please enter the url again.]]></message>
		<!-- tooltip messages -->
		<message id="search_panel_help"><![CDATA[Run an instant global performance check of your site! Simply enter the web address below and put it to test. You will see a comparison between the actual performance of your site versus an estimated performance with Akamai's dynamic site and application acceleration capabilities.        
This version of DV4 provides additional cities and regional views tailored to your target market.]]>
        </message>
		<message id="weeklong_graph_help"><![CDATA[Provides a benchmark for expected performance improvement over one week from a given city to the region in which the Origin is based.]]></message>
		<message id="average_global_performance_help"><![CDATA[Compares estimated performance over Akamai with actual performance direct to Origin. Breaks down total page download time in to connection time, first byte time and download time.]]></message>
		<message id="performance_by_city_help"><![CDATA[Compares estimated performance between Akamai and Origin, per city.]]></message>
		<message id="performance_by_region_help"><![CDATA[Compares estimated average performance between Akamai and Origin, per continent.]]></message>
		<message id="m4"><![CDATA[Dots on the map indicate the locations of Akamai testing agents. Click on these dots to simulate end user connection times from those locations.]]></message>
		<message id="email_result"><![CDATA[Email the results.]]></message>
		<message id="print_result"><![CDATA[Print the results.]]></message>
		<message id="weeklong_performance_benchmark"><![CDATA[Provides a benchmark for expected performance improvement over one week from a given city to the region in which the Origin is based.]]></message>
		<message id="save_pdf"><![CDATA[Save as PDF]]></message>
		<!-- Loading messages -->
		<message id="measure_default_peformance">
			<![CDATA[Measuring the site's default performance]]>
		</message>
		<message id="weeklong_report_request">
			<![CDATA[Submitting Weeklong Report Request]]>
		</message>
		<message id="previous_weeklong_list_loading">
			<![CDATA[Previous Weeklong Report list loading]]>
		</message>
		<message id="weeklong_report_loading">
			<![CDATA[Weeklong Report loading]]>
		</message>
		<message id="additional_site_revenue_per_month">
			<![CDATA[Based on performance-driven site abandonment rates as captured in Forrester 2009 eCommerce]]>
		</message>
		<message id="calculate_improvement">
			<![CDATA[Calculating performance improvement metrics]]>
		</message>
		<message id="present_improvement">
			<![CDATA[Presenting performance improvement]]>
		</message>
	</help>